The superhero movie to end all superhero movies. Hopefully.
Teen Titans Go! To the Movies is a animation, action,
comedy film directed by Aaron Horvath.
All the major DC superheroes are starring in their own films, all but the Teen Titans, so Robin is determined
to remedy this situation by getting over his role as a sidekick and becoming a movie star.
Thus, with a few madcap ideas and an inspirational song in their hearts,
the Teen Titans head to Hollywood to fulfill their dreams.
Beast Boy (voice), played by Greg Cipes.
Robin (voice), played by Scott Menville.
Cyborg (voice), played by Khary Payton.
Raven (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Starfire (voice), played by Hynden Walch.
Slade (voice), played by Will Arnett.
Teen Titans Go!
To the Movies is a 2018 American animated superhero musical comedy film
featuring the DC Comics superhero team, the Teen Titans.
Based on the Cartoon Network animated television series Teen
Titans Go!, it was produced by Warner Bros.
Animation and DC Entertainment and distributed by Warner Bros.
The film was directed by Peter Rida Michail and Aaron Horvath
and written by Michael Jelenic and Horvath.
It features the voices of Greg Cipes, Scott Menville, Khary Payton, Tara Strong, and Hynden Walch, reprising their respective
roles from the series, while Will Arnett  and Kristen Bell join the cast, with the former serving as a producer.
Taking place during the events of the fifth season of the television series, the film follows the Teen Titans,
who attempt to have a movie made about them in Hollywood while dealing with supervillain Slade.
Warner Bros.
Pictures first announced the film in September 2017 with the
series' voice cast set to reprise their roles.
Arnett and Bell were added to the cast in leading roles a month later.
Teen Titans Go!
To the Movies premiered in the TCL Chinese Theatre on July 22,
2018, and was theatrically released by Warner Bros.
Pictures in the United States on July 27, 2018.
It grossed $52.1 million worldwide on a $10 million budget.
It received positive reviews from critics, who praised the
story, humor, music, and entertainment value.
This is one of the posthumous releases for longtime DC producer
Benjamin Melniker, who died five months before its release.
The film explores themes of movie business, superhero,
time travel, slapstick comedy, hollywood.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.